Sometimes to find yourself you need to get a little lost.
Hector and the Search for Happiness is a adventure,
drama, comedy film directed by Peter Chelsom.
Hector is a quirky psychiatrist who has become
increasingly tired of his humdrum life.
As he tells his girlfriend, Clara, he feels like a fraud: he hasn’t really tasted life, and
yet he’s offering advice to patients who are just not getting any happier.
So Hector decides to break out of his deluded and routine driven life.
Armed with buckets of courage and child-like curiosity, he embarks on a global quest
in hopes of uncovering the elusive secret formula for true happiness.
And so begins a larger than life adventure with riotously funny results.
Hector, played by Simon Pegg.
Clara, played by Rosamund Pike.
Agnes, played by Toni Collette.
Edward, played by Stellan Skarsgård.
Professor Coreman, played by Christopher Plummer.
Diego Baresco, played by Jean Reno.
Hector and the Search for Happiness is a 2014 comedy-drama film directed by Peter Chelsom and co-written by
Chelsom with Tinker Lindsay and Maria von Heland, based on François Lelord's novel of the same name.
The film stars Simon Pegg as Hector and Rosamund Pike as Clara.
The film explores themes of china, africa, routine, narration, office.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.